Presented by Viki
Engineering at Viki.
We disrupt & define the future of TV worldwide. One line of code at a time.
Who We Are
The Engineering Team at Viki works on developing and maintaining the backend behind viki.com - a global TV site powered by a volunteer community of avid fans.
Launched in December 2010, we have over 2 billion video streams and more than 400 million words translated.
We0 are not obsessed by any particular technology.
We believe cool technologies might not get the job done, the right technologies do.
We1 use Ruby, Node.js, Golang, AngularJS, EmberJS with PostgreSQL, Redis and RabbitMQ.
We2 make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.
We3 make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.
We4 make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.
We5 make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.
We6 make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.
We7 make sure our code are highly decoupled through message queue infrastructure, service-oriented architectures and proper design patterns.